<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts-rss on Adventure Time!</title>
    <link>http://example.com/posts/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts-rss on Adventure Time!</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2016 00:16:57 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://example.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Testing out Forestry.io with Github Pages</title>
      <link>http://example.com/posts/testing-out-forestry-io-with-github-pages/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2016 00:16:57 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.com/posts/testing-out-forestry-io-with-github-pages/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m testing out Forestry.io with my Github Pages to see if I&amp;rsquo;ll like using it to make it easier for me to keep up with blogging.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Food Chain (Season 6)</title>
      <link>http://example.com/posts/season-6-food-chain/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.com/posts/season-6-food-chain/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The episode begins with candy children that have bodies resembling different shapes sliding down a slide, shouting with excitement. The kids are viewed from an horizontal angle in the next scene as they go through a playground-like structure. Finn and Jake are examining the &amp;lsquo;Catapilla Family&amp;rsquo;. After watching Princess Bubblegum teach the children about the Food Chain, they head to the snack bar as Finn found Princess Bubblegum&amp;rsquo;s class useless.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;a change&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While they&amp;rsquo;re walking Magic Man appears behind the two without them knowing, and transforms them into birds. After singing an electronic version of &amp;ldquo;&lt;a href=&#34;http://adventuretime.wikia.com/wiki/Der_H%C3%B6lle_Rache_kocht_in_meinem_Herzen&#34;&gt;Der Hölle Rache kocht in meinem Herzen&lt;/a&gt;,&amp;rdquo; they fly down below to a place with an oasis on it. Jake eats some caterpillars, which disgusts Finn. After that Finn tries eating the caterpillars and pukes on the ground. In the next scene, Finn and Jake are shown to be very chubby and sitting on the ground lazily. Finn becomes confused for why he became full from eating few caterpillars. Jake informs him that they have been eating for hours. Soon, Finn and Jake notice a shadow on the ground that gradually becomes bigger. They look up to see a big bird trying to attack them. Finn and Jake dodge this attack and attempt to fly away. However, because of Finn&amp;rsquo;s chubby body, Finn is not able to fly and skids across the ground. As the big bird flies closer, Finn cowers. The big bird does not recognize Finn and flies onward. As Finn tries to fly away, the big bird notices and flies towards him once again. Just as the big bird was close enough to strike, Magic Man converts Finn into the big bird.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finn then flies next to Jake. Jake does not recognize him, stating him as big and old. Finn hallucinates Jake as meat. Finn drools awfully, and states that Jake looks awesome and tasty. Finn asks Jake if he wants to go inside his mouth. Jake accepts and sits in his mouth. He states that Finn has a lot of saliva. Finn tries to eat Jake before he could escape from Finn&amp;rsquo;s mouth. Finn attempts again to eat him. Finn elevates lower until he hits the ground. He lays on the ground while the sun sets, stating how hungry he is, and dies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, Finn is turned into hundreds of bacteria. The bacteria notices the dead body of the big bird as food and eats it. Jake is also turned into a bacterium and states that Finn eating the big bird is disgusting. The bacteria becomes full after the big bird results as a skeleton. The bacteria is then swept away by a gust of wind. Finn and Jake then find themselves turned into flowers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finn and Jake sing &amp;ldquo;&lt;a href=&#34;http://adventuretime.wikia.com/wiki/We%27re_Plants&#34;&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re Plants&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;rdquo; during the song, caterpillars eat Finn and Jake&amp;rsquo;s leaves. Small birds come to eat the caterpillars. Finn and Jake are then turned into caterpillars.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finn and Jake spot &lt;a href=&#34;http://adventuretime.wikia.com/wiki/Erin&#34;&gt;Erin&lt;/a&gt; who faints from the heat. Finn crawls to Erin quickly, madly in love with her. Finn and Jake crawl with her in search of an oasis. Erin faints again, and Jake finds an oasis. Finn, Erin, and Jake eat the leaves in the oasis. After a short discussion, Erin and Finn decide to get married.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The scene changes into a leaf with a group of caterpillars with Jake hosting the marriage. Finn agrees to the marriage and everyone cheers. Suddenly, two birds are shown flying to the leaf, eating the caterpillars. Finn and Jake then changes into the birds eating the caterpillars until Finn was back into reality. Finn had caterpillars stuffed in his mouth in which he spitted them out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Back into the reality, Finn realizes the lesson of the Food Chain and sings &amp;ldquo;&lt;a href=&#34;http://adventuretime.wikia.com/wiki/Food_Chain_(song)&#34;&gt;Food Chain&lt;/a&gt;&amp;rdquo;, which PB soon joins singing with him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The end shows Finn transforming into a bird-caterpillar-plant-bacteria hybrid while the kids leave due to boredom, once again entering the slide seen in the beginning.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Tower (Season 6)</title>
      <link>http://example.com/posts/season-6-the-tower/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.com/posts/season-6-the-tower/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The episode starts with Finn trying to make spaghetti with a bulky candy arm. His bulky arm doesn&amp;rsquo;t help Finn and he starts destroying things and as he continues to mess things up, he gets frustrated and his candy arm explodes. &lt;a href=&#34;http://adventuretime.wikia.com/wiki/Jake&#34;&gt;Jake&lt;/a&gt;comes down stairs, hoping for the spaghetti, but instead sees the mess and tells him that he should just take his time and listen to his &amp;ldquo;Melon Heart.&amp;rdquo; Finn then says he wants to go to space so he can take &lt;a href=&#34;http://adventuretime.wikia.com/wiki/Martin&#34;&gt;his father&lt;/a&gt;&amp;rsquo;s arm. Jake tells him not to do this but to just relax and think and that he&amp;rsquo;s going to the store to buy replacement kitchen supplies for the ones Finn broke. Finn goes outside the tree fort and he lies on the ground. He starts to talk to himself and then suddenly he notices a pile of rocks forming behind him and that there is an odd, sightly transparent arm, where his real arm used to be. He then decides to use this arm to build a tower into space to find his dad.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As Jake is returning home, the tower has grown considerably and &lt;a href=&#34;http://adventuretime.wikia.com/wiki/Princess_Bubblegum&#34;&gt;Princess Bubblegum&lt;/a&gt; is there and tells Jake that Finn&amp;rsquo;s got a new arm, what she believes to be a telekinetic electro-emotional prosthesis and is dangerous and could hurt him and other people around him. Jake shakes off the notion and says what Finn&amp;rsquo;s doing is healthy and he should just be left alone. As Finn continues his tower he enters the cloud house of a &lt;a href=&#34;http://adventuretime.wikia.com/wiki/Cloud_People&#34;&gt;Cloud person&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;a href=&#34;http://adventuretime.wikia.com/wiki/Carroll&#34;&gt;She&lt;/a&gt; tells Finn to leave, and when he doesn&amp;rsquo;t, blasts him with lightning with her gun. This moves the house out of the tower and the cloud person then says that Finn must be, &amp;ldquo;One of those swimmers,&amp;rdquo; and leaves.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The next day large chunks of Ooo&amp;rsquo;s landscape are missing because of the tower, including a rookery of &lt;a href=&#34;http://adventuretime.wikia.com/wiki/Penguins&#34;&gt;penguins&lt;/a&gt;. The cloud person from the day prior returns to Finn, introduces herself as Carroll and apologizes and asks if he&amp;rsquo;s really going to take his father&amp;rsquo;s arm. Finn states that he is and the cloud person talks about how she was water once and how swimmers would always be swimming in her, so she got evaporated and became air. She then tells Finn he should let it go, runaway, and hate his life like she has.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the ground &lt;a href=&#34;http://adventuretime.wikia.com/wiki/BMO&#34;&gt;BMO&lt;/a&gt; asks Jake what Finn is doing (not before getting crushed into the ground by a falling ice block). Jake says Finn&amp;rsquo;s just working some stuff out and that it&amp;rsquo;s completely healthy, which is directed at PB who is working on some sort of device. PB disagrees and says that Finn could get hurt. As Finn&amp;rsquo;s tower has finally reached the atmosphere, Carroll asks what it&amp;rsquo;s like up there and wonders if she should become space ice. Finn, who is extremely oxygen deprived, sees a similar looking portal to the one the &lt;a href=&#34;http://adventuretime.wikia.com/wiki/Void_Caster&#34;&gt;Void Caster&lt;/a&gt; made in &amp;ldquo;&lt;a href=&#34;http://adventuretime.wikia.com/wiki/Escape_from_the_Citadel&#34;&gt;Escape from the Citadel&lt;/a&gt;,&amp;rdquo; but suddenly a bright light comes at him and he blacks out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finn then wakes up in what seems to be a space ship and walks to the next room to see his &amp;lsquo;father&amp;rsquo; watching TV. Finn surprises his father and punches him into unconsciousness and tries to take his arm. As Martin moans about his favorite arm, Finn changes his mind and it is revealed that Martin was really a disguised PB. She says she tricked Finn and took him to the &lt;a href=&#34;http://adventuretime.wikia.com/wiki/Candy_Kingdom&#34;&gt;Candy Kingdom&lt;/a&gt; fallout bunker, and since he had so little oxygen that he was already hallucinating, the trick was easy to pull off.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finn returns home, with his telekinetic arm gone, and tells Jake that he&amp;rsquo;s calmed down. Jake says that&amp;rsquo;s great and asks if Finn wants to do the honors of taking down the tower. Finn says he would and removes a plank of wood near the base of the tower, which then collapses sideways, destroying a large portion of the Candy Kingdom, to the shock of Finn and Jake. The episode ends with Princess Bubblegum screaming, &amp;ldquo;AHHH! MY ARM!&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>